- Previously on "The Ark"...
- Their message sounded
like they're in trouble.
- You're heading down there.
Is it safe?
- Of course it's safe.
- They're all dead.
- Admiral Ben Hammond
of "Ark 4."
- Meet Milan Petrovic.
head of Homebase 1 security.
- I believe Kelly Fowler
should be freed.
- I have to go out
in the exploration zone.
You want to come?
- We're pinned down
and won't be able to make it
to the shuttle.
- "Pinned down"? By what?
- Alien bloody creatures. mate.
[both scream]
I'm gonna pull 'em off
this way.
- No!
- Brice!
- Run!
- I'm so sorry. Eva.
but he's dead.
[indistinct chatter]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- I wish we had a funeral
for Lieutenant Brice
like we did for Doc Morozov.
- Brice always thought
he was gonna die young
from Klampkins and made it
very clear he didn't want us
wallowing in grief for him.
- And yet here we are.
- Well. I mean. I didn't know
him as well as you lot did.
but Brice always seemed like
a "raise a glass of scotch
and celebrate me" kind of guy.
- No. no.
A whiskey from the homeland
tasted like piss.
[chuckles]
- Which do you think
he hated more.
Scotch or William Trust?
[laughter]
- Hammond to senior staff.
Report to the bridge.
- Can he do that.
just call a meeting?
- Apparently. he thinks he can.
[dramatic music]
- [sighs] So I've been
reviewing your logs
and I--
What are you looking at?
- Uh. sir.
♪ ♪
- Sorry. it was
the only free cabin.
Your lieutenant
was the same size.
As I said. I read your logs.
and I want to set course
for the Tyson system.
- Wait. hold on.
Who's in charge?
- [chuckles]
Sharon. obviously.
- I respect your
field promotion. Captain.
but I still outrank you.
- In what?
The GSA is gone.
- Excuse me?
- You know
the GSA charter. Admiral.
It clearly states we were to
get humanity to new homeworlds
and relinquish control
to civilian governance.
♪ ♪
- Then how does this all work?
- "Ark 1" is crewed by a mix
of former GSA and EF volunteers
who've chosen to follow
Captain Garnet.
- "Ark 1" is now
a Homebase 1 ship.
not a GSA ship.
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry I overstepped.
It won't happen again.
- Good.
- But if I may?
Did you know that
when Evelyn Maddox fled
Homebase 1. she set a course
in the shuttle nav system?
- Yes.
- So why haven't you
investigated?
- I thought it was
more important to make contact
with the Ross colony.
- Even though
I warned you not to come?
- Well. that's a weird way
to say thanks.
- "Ark 1's" mission
is to save people at risk
and bring them to Homebase.
- Okay. and don't you think
there might be people
where Maddox was going?
- Yeah. people
that want to kill us.
- Or people who are suffering.
just as the people of Homebase
were suffering
before you intervened.
- So you want
to investigate now?
- Tyson 5E.
It can't support life.
- So it's likely
a rendezvous point.
- Exactly.
Whoever Maddox was meeting
might still be there
waiting for her.
We can drop out of FTL here.
right behind Tyson's moon.
- To hide us
from any ships in orbit.
- Solid plan.
Okay. let's set a course.
♪ ♪
Admiral. a moment?
You read my logs.
I read your files.
I appreciate your experience.
- But not enough to follow me?
- No.
But you'd clearly be an asset.
I could use a number two.
♪ ♪
[thudding]
[person grunting]
- Kelly?
Where are--
[gasps]
What am I wearing?
- I don't know.
- You changed my clothes?
- No.
I just woke up a minute ago.
[thudding]
- Why aren't you wearing
these weird clothes?
- Again. I don't know.
We were in the woods.
There was a flash of light.
and here we are.
[grunts]
[thudding]
[watch beeps]
- No signal.
Okay.
[tense music]
- My implants are on. and
I'm not even making a scratch.
- There's no doors.
How did we get in here?
- What I want to know is...
♪ ♪
How do we get out?
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- Captain Garnet.
Ian and I have a report on--
- Crewman. brief me first.
- Oh.
- Seriously?
- Chain of command.
As her second. it's my job to
make sure her life is easier.
- "Her second"?
- Thank you. but we do things
a little differently here.
They can report to me directly.
- Captain. I gave up sunlight
and fresh air at Homebase
to take orders from you.
- And I'm still in command.
- But you gave Brice's job
to some guy who hitched a ride?
- Let's all remember.
the admiral earned his rank.
We can benefit
from his experience.
- My training is
in peaceful missions.
same as Captain Garnet.
Is that good enough
for you. crewman?
[tense music]
You have a report
for the captain?
- Oh. uh. yeah.
um. we've been analyzing
the data on the solar shields
we created at Ross.
I think we can make them
sustainable.
- Yeah. with a bit of work.
we can calibrate them
to protect us
from different wavelengths
of radiation
and electromagnetic pulses.
- And maybe even small impacts
from solid matter
like asteroid fragments.
- How about impact
from artillery?
- Well. what ever happened
to peaceful missions?
- I want peace.
Doesn't mean
everyone else does.
[indistinct chatter]
- Uh-oh.
I know that look.
- This?
This is my normal.
handsome. everyday look.
- It's your
"dying to say something
but biting your tongue" look.
- No. it's not my place.
I want to respect
your boundaries.
- Ha. says the man trying
to nickname me Curly
because he dreamed it.
- Yeah. about that...
I think I understand now
why you think our time
in the coma wasn't real.
I spent decades
learning astrophysics. right?
Now it turns out
it was just my brain
creating fake science.
So what else
did my brain make up?
- I appreciate that.
But I still want to know
what's on your mind.
- Isn't it obvious?
I don't trust Hammond.
- Because he tried
to take command?
- Because he backed down
too easily.
I mean. does that sound
like any admiral you ever met?
♪ ♪
- Leaving FTL in three. two...
now.
- [scoffs] Well. you cut that
a little close. Kimi.
- Plan called for us to get as
near to the moon as possible.
- And we got here in one piece.
Call that good work.
Lieutenant Joma.
- Passive scans only. Alicia.
Let's try not to alert anyone
to our presence.
- It might be
a little bit late for that.
- It's "Ark 22."
They have energy weapons.
- You remember what I said
about people
wanting to kill us?
- Can your shield stop them?
- No. we're still
upgrading them.
- We're being hailed.
- Charge FTL fast.
Send them to my screen.
♪ ♪
- Oh.
Smart hiding place.
Didn't work but smart.
Let me guess--you're looking
for Evelyn Maddox?
- Not exactly.
I'm Captain Sharon Garnet
of "Ark 1."
- Kurtis Drake.
leader of "Ark 22."
- We were investigating
why Evelyn Maddox may--
- You're a clone.
you and the gentleman
at your side.
- Uh. what makes you think
I'm a clone?
- [chuckles] Well. because
I'm married to you.
I'm married to one of you.
- [giggles]
- This is. um. Jill.
- Hi. there.
Is it conceited to say
you're very beautiful?
Even in those drab colors.
[laughter]
- Oh. and we do have J6-82s
on board as well.
Richard. Clark.
come and say hi.
- Oh.
Hello. brother.
Hey.
- Yeah.
- Did you know there were
other clones of you?
- N--
- Come on over.
It'd be lovely to have you.
- No. we don't give up
our people.
- You misunderstand.
This is not a request.
- He's charging weapons.
- Fire on my mark.
Three. two. one.
- All right. we'll go.
- We'll come. We'll come over.
[Jill sighs]
- Good.
I look forward to it.
[Jill giggles]
Don't take too long.
- No. you can't go over there.
- We don't have a choice.
Admiral Hammond has command
while I'm gone.
- Really?
- Those are my orders.
Keep this ship safe.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- This could be
a good thing. right?
I mean. means there's
more of us in the universe.
- Who have a whole lot
of weapons pointed at us.
- Yeah. there is that.
- I don't like this.
We should have hidden weapons
in the shuttle.
- Weapons or not.
they're outnumbered.
- Clear of "Ark 1."
- Godspeed. Captain.
"Ark 1." out.
- Okay. so what's your plan
to get them home?
- Is the FTL charged?
- Yeah. but--
[ship whirs. pulses]
- Ugh.
I really don't like that guy.
[tense music]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[knock on door]
[knocking continues]
♪ ♪
- It's a little early. Felix.
- Yes. well. I've been trying
to reach you since last night.
- My WD is off.
What do you need?
- Um...
♪ ♪
- You're watching video
of Brice's death?
- Garnet sent me the footage
from the shuttle's
hull cameras.
- Have you slept?
Don't torture yourself
like this. Eva.
- I have to see it.
- May I ask you
to take a break?
I have something to show you.
Please.
♪ ♪
It's a new concept.
- Okay. what it is?
- There they are.
- Come here.
♪ ♪
- I'm sorry.
- I don't normally like people
invading my personal space.
However.
given the circumstances...
♪ ♪
He was a good man. I guess.
- So what did you have
to show me. Felix?
- That you are not alone.
[tender music]
- Thank you.
- Sit down.
♪ ♪
- You eaten?
You should eat.
- Stop mothering her.
- I'm doctoring her.
- I could definitely eat.
Who are we waiting for?
- [sighs] Angus.
I couldn't get a hold of him.
- Neither could I.
- Well. I'm not gonna
wait for him.
I'm gonna go
and get some breakfast.
- You do that.
- Hey. you want some coffee?
- Who do you think put us here?
- [grunts]
I'm more worried
about what put us here.
- Yeah. you have a point.
These walls are too smooth
to be natural.
They had to have been
machine-honed.
which means someone
pretty advanced built these.
God. I just--I wonder about
the light from these crystals.
Is it electric.
naturally occurring.
filtered through
from some different--
Can you stop that?
You said
it's not making a dent.
Kelly. I said stop--
Man. Kelly.
you're trashing your hand.
- It doesn't hurt that much.
- You're obviously in pain.
Take a break.
- It's not my hand that hurts.
It's my ears.
With my implants on.
I hear this awful noise.
- Turn the implants off.
Besides. you don't want to go
into organ failure.
- Whoever took us will be back.
I need to be ready to fight.
- I'll fight them off till
you get your implants back on.
- [chuckles]
That's funny.
Oh. you're serious.
- Turn them off.
[watch beeps]
Better?
- I guess.
At least I'm not hearing
that screeching sound anymore.
[piercing tone]
[gasps]
Something's wrong.
I'm still hearing those sounds.
- Wait. I hear them. too. now.
Wait. That's what they sounded
like with your implants on?
It's not that bad.
[piercing tone intensifies]
Aah!
Ah. strike that.
- And so I think we should take
a moment of silence
for James Brice
and Dr. Morozov.
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
- Now we must move forward.
I'm afraid we have
some more troubling news.
Two of Homebase 1's citizens
are missing.
Angus Medford and Kelly Fowler
went to the expanded zone
and never returned.
We lost contact.
- You know what
probably happened.
Kelly went psycho
and killed her ex-boyfriend.
- Let's not jump
to conclusions.
- I spent 3 years
on "Ark 15" with her.
We can't trust her.
- It's true!
[all murmuring]
- Stop.
These speculations
about Ms. Fowler end now.
She's proven
herself repeatedly.
- What's important
is to find them.
- I'm taking volunteers
for a search party.
Thank you.
We'll leave after
our last order of business.
- It's no secret that.
with the arrival
of "Ark 1" and "EF2."
has led to some growing
problems in our colony.
Our council has appointed
a new sheriff. Milan Petrovic.
[cheers and applause]
Some of you worked
with Milan on "Ark 11"
when he was head of security.
We're sure that he will do
as well at this position.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [breathing rapidly]
- Sanji?
Sanji. what's wrong?
- It's him.
- Him--who?
- The sheriff.
- What?
- He's my ex-husband.
Hey. hey. are you crazy?
- Sanji. I'm gonna talk to him.
- No.
- Sanji!
- No. I need to handle
this myself.
- No. I'll go.
I'll talk to him.
- Just give me
a moment to think.
- Hello. Sanji.
- Stay away from her.
- Damir.
- Let me talk to him.
- I'll handle this.
- Sanji.
- Alone!
- Okay.
I'll be in the dorm
if you need me.
♪ ♪
- [sniffs]
It's good to see you.
Um. can we talk somewhere
more private?
- Here's fine.
- Fair enough.
Um...
I owe you an apology.
♪ ♪
I'm sober now.
I know that doesn't excuse
anything. but...
I want you to know
I'm not the man I was.
- Good.
I'm not the woman I was either.
So leave me the hell alone.
- If you go near Sanji
ever again. I will end you.
You hear me. you piece of shit?
- Loud and clear.
What. you gonna hit me.
or you gonna let me go?
What's it gonna be. hmm?
[tense music]
[chuckles]
Good to meet you. Damir.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- For someone so concerned
with GSA protocols...
- I can't believe you just
deserted Captain Garnet...
[overlapping speech]
- That's a direct violation
of GSA codes.
I guarantee you
no one will stand for it.
- Are you finished. or are you
just taking a breath?
- [scoffs]
- How can you joke right now?
- I'm actually trying
to keep my patience
as you voice your concerns.
- You abandoned
Captain Garnet and Ian.
- You heard
the Captain's orders.
She said keep the ship safe.
- Yeah. not run away.
- Ms. Nevins. your shields
still aren't repaired.
- What does that
have to do with--
- And we don't
have any weapons.
- We weren't under attack.
- Drake had what he wanted.
There was no reason to assume
that he wouldn't open up fire.
- And there's no reason
to assume that he would.
- I won't risk the lives of
the entire ship for two people!
- We just risked this entire
ship to save you on Ross.
- And that was a bad move!
You lost your doctor
and your number two.
The math doesn't work.
- People aren't math.
- Sometimes they are.
On Ross. Garnet traded
two lives to save one.
Math.
She put me in charge
because she knew
I wouldn't make
the same mistake.
- Or you're happy she's gone...
so you can have this ship.
- [scoffs]
- Given the stress
of what's happened.
I'm gonna pretend
I didn't hear that...
Lieutenant Joma.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Thank you so much
for coming over.
- Yeah. well.
we didn't have a choice.
- I never would have fired.
Yeah. but sometimes
a show of force keeps people
from getting the wrong idea.
- Oh. I see.
and the armed guards--
what kind of idea is
that supposed to give us?
- Oh. just a precaution.
I-I wanted to greet you
privately.
but my wife--
yeah. she worries.
- WDs. please.
- Is that necessary?
- We'll keep them safe
in our security lockup.
♪ ♪
- Can you roll up your sleeves?
- Back off.
- It's okay.
We don't use J6-82s for organs.
- I have a name. and it's Ian.
- Excellent.
I encourage you even
to take a last name.
- What's that for?
- We need blood samples
to make sure you're not Gen-3s.
- Well. we're not.
Otherwise. we would have
already developed psychosis.
- That's not true.
There are the occasional
late bloomers.
Easy way or hard way--
up to you.
♪ ♪
You two don't seem to know
much about clone science.
- We know enough.
Original humans
are Generation 1.
and us clones are Gen-2s.
- And clones made
from Gen-2 DNA are Gen-3.
- Very good.
And Gen-3 brain cells
are unstable.
and they do develop psychosis.
They're dangerous.
which is why we have
to make sure you aren't one.
- How do you know
Evelyn Maddox?
- Evelyn was
a business acquaintance.
She sold me this Ark
during Earth's last days.
Joke's on her.
What does money matter now?
- Why were you meeting her?
- I have no idea.
She called me. but something
tells me she. um...
she won't be showing up
just now. will she?
- [scoffs] You could have told
us that over comms.
- Well. then I wouldn't have
the pleasure
to meet you lovelies in person.
- What do you want from us?
- It's not what
I want from you.
It's what you want from me.
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
- Ian?
- Oh. I see it.
I don't quite believe it.
- This ship is a safe haven
for clones.
- Wait. are you saying everyone
on this ship is a clone?
- It's great. isn't it?
Guys. how are you?
[both laugh]
Thank you so much for dinner.
- Ah! [scoffs]
- No. it was delicious.
It was perfect.
- I never imagined
so many clones survived Earth.
It's amazing.
- Yeah. I mean. besides
my brothers in the lab.
I've never even met
another clone like me.
- Same. I always thought
it was just me and Denise.
I wonder how many
of each Gen-2 models were made.
- A lot.
The original humans designed
clones to be exploited--
you know. labor. parts.
experimentation.
- So they wouldn't go
to all that expense
only to create a few of us.
- That's right.
Cloning was a business.
and if they hadn't cut corners
by using Gen-2s
to create Gen-3s.
the business
would have never been outlawed.
- I do have to admit.
it does make a nice change
to see clones walking around
with smiles on their faces.
- So this is the part
where you thank me
for saving you from that ship.
- Saving us?
She was the freaking captain.
- Of a GSA Ark?
They haven't exactly
been allies
to the clone cause. have they?
- The GSA doesn't exist
anymore. mate.
We've got a new colony now.
Homebase 1.
It's pretty nice. too.
and clones are welcome there.
- And valued.
just like anyone else.
just like we are welcome
on "Ark 1."
- Oh. okay.
Then why did they
leave you behind?
♪ ♪
- Working on a rescue plan?
- If the admiral wants math.
I'll give him math.
- I've served under men
like Hammond before.
He's not changing his mind.
- I wish Lieutenant Brice
was still here.
What gives him the right
to decide how we proceed?
- Garnet did
when she left him in charge.
- [scoffs] Well. he'll change
his tune when I show him this.
- I hope so.
but. um. just in case...
here's a plan B.
It's always good to have
a backup plan.
- Are you searching
for inhabitable worlds
to settle on?
- Who's to say
we haven't found one?
- Is that your old man?
- Oh. no. no.
That's. um. Kurtis Drake prime.
the inventor
of cloning science.
But in a way. he's the--
he's the father of us all.
- You're his clone.
- Yes. uh. but do not mistake
my work for the creator's.
He sought wealth.
- And what do you seek?
- To build a place
for us to live in harmony
without oppression
from the original humans.
- Clone society.
- Well. forget the fact
that your model was designed
for the rigors of space
or that you were made
to be an organ donor.
Here we can be
whatever we want--
doctors. scientists. poets.
Here we're free.
- We have a colony
you could join.
- I mean. the two of you might
be accepted. but all of us?
Old prejudices die hard.
Captain.
- Morgan to Drake.
Can you come to medbay?
- On my way. Doctor.
Oh. here's the mess hall.
The food is delicious.
Go on in. Relax.
Have a meal.
I'm sure you'll have
more questions later.
- No guards?
- We have nothing to hide.
[indistinct chatter]
[mysterious music]
♪ ♪
- Uh...
[knock on door]
- I figured it out.
- You figured out what?
There are a lot
of calculations on here
that fall outside
of my expertise.
- Alicia has a plan to save
Captain Garnet and Ian.
- Oh.
I'm listening.
- A while ago. William Trust
created a weaponized EM pulse.
- According to your logs.
it nearly fried your engines.
- Yes. but I figured out
how to re-create it
in a way that we can fire off
three shots safely.
- Wow.
Three shots.
And what about your shields?
Have you found a way
to recalibrate them
to withstand "Ark 22" weapons?
- No. but--
- All right. stop.
- But if the EM
disables their weapons--
- You're dismissed.
- Sir. no one is happy we've
left two of our own behind.
- We've had this conversation.
I'm not gonna risk the lives
of the entire ship on an if.
- Is this your final decision?
- Yes. it's my final decision.
Now. unless you can--
[groans]
- I was really hoping
we wouldn't have to do plan B.
[dramatic music]
- No one in or out until
we've got our captain back.
[keypad beeps]
- Time is not on our side.
If Kelly and Angus
suffered an accident.
they'll need food. water.
and medical attention.
We should pair up
and widen our search.
- I'll search with you. Felix.
- I think not.
- [chuckles]
Who told you. Sanji or Marsh?
- I would have never approved
you as sheriff
if I'd known who you are.
- Who I am. Felix.
is a guy who wants to help
you find two missing people.
Hey.
Do you want my help or not?
[eerie music]
♪ ♪
[piercing tone]
- This is a torture technique.
- My WD is picking up patterns
in the noise.
There's harmonic variations
at frequencies
outside the range
of human hearing.
- So what does that mean?
- It explains
why you could hear it
when your implants were on.
- How is that helpful?
- I have no idea.
I don't know.
[keypad beeping. lock clicks]
[keys clacking]
- Oh. Markovic.
I'm glad you're here.
I could use your help
to recalibrate the spectrograph
to run a chemical analysis
on the tablet.
- Maybe later.
- This tablet
could be the greatest discovery
of our lifetime.
maybe human history.
So what could possibly be
more interesting than that?
Well...
maybe working on the tablet
will help take your mind
off your grief.
- Something happened to Brice
as the shuttle took off.
- Eva.
- Just watch.
First. an exhaust fume.
and there. he's gone.
- I don't want to be harsh.
but. uh. something
was eating him.
- Then where is his body?
- I don't know.
I guess the creature
dragged it away?
- Or he--he walked away.
- Eva...
I understand.
I really do.
I desperately miss
Helena and Cat.
but I've had to accept
that they're gone.
just like you have to accept
that Lieutenant Brice is gone.
Now. come on.
[keys clacking]
Come and help me
with the tablet. please?
- No.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
- Sun's getting low.
and it's still hot as hell.
Everyone's exhausted.
- We can't stop
until we find them.
- Look. I get it.
Angus and Kelly
are your people.
but we've been at this all day.
- They're our people.
- Sure.
But so are they.
Look. everyone here
needs a meal
and a good night's sleep.
We can continue
the search tomorrow.
Come on. man.
tell me you're not tired.
- I'm going to keep on looking.
You can do what you want.
- Well. you're a better man
than me. Felix.
Okay. everyone who's ready
to call it for the night.
follow me.
[whistles]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- I can't take
much more of this!
- What?
- I said. I can't take
more of this!
- Me either!
[piercing tone]
[tone stops]
[gasping]
Maybe someone heard us?
- Or the next torture
is about to begin.
[rumbling]
Get behind me.
[watch beeps]
♪ ♪
- Maybe we're
supposed to go out?
- It could be a trap.
♪ ♪
[gas hisses]
[both groaning]
♪ ♪
[deep rumbling]
Oh. shit.
- Angus!
- [grunting. shouting]
Maybe let's stay in here.
[light music]
♪ ♪
- Welcome aboard.
- Ah.
- Thank you.
- Happy to be here.
Something's wrong here. right?
- Yeah. Drake's pushing the
hard sell a little too much.
- Hey. girl!
[giggles]
I've totally got clothes
in your size
if you. like.
ever want to borrow them.
- Uh. y-you know I do.
- [exhales sharply]
I knew it.
♪ ♪
- Have you noticed there's
no other clones of Drake here.
but there are of everyone else?
- Yeah. we're gonna need
to figure out
his connection to Maddox.
get our WDs.
and signal "Ark 1."
- You don't really believe
we can rely
on Hammond for help?
- If we can make contact.
uh. maybe we can figure out
a rescue plan
that won't put "Ark 1"
in danger.
- [sighs]
Fair enough.
- [chuckles]
- Divide and conquer?
- Yes. I'll get
into the security lockup
and grab our WDs.
- Right. I'll go
to the server room.
see if there's
any communications logs
with Maddox.
- I don't know.
Going to the bridge
might look suspicious.
- What about Drake's quarters?
Maybe there's a WD there
with some information on it.
- Good idea.
Meet at the shuttle.
- Yeah.
- What have you got for me?
- I ran the blood sample
three times.
[dramatic music]
- [scoffs] We finally found
what we were looking for.
♪ ♪
[device beeps]
- [chuckles]
- [yelps]
- [gasps]
- You're not Clark.
- Uh. yes. I am.
- No. you're not.
- No. I'm not.
- [gasps]
You're one of the clones
Kurtis freed from "Ark 1."
- "Freed"?
[scoffs]
Kidnapped. more like.
Oh. no.
No. I wouldn't do that
if I was you.
- Kurtis is gonna throw
your ass out the airlock
for sneaking into our quarters.
- Oh. yeah?
And tell me. what do you think
would make Drake angrier--
me sneaking in here
or you dressed like that
waiting for a guy named Clark?
- [sighs]
What do you want?
- What's Drake's connection
to Maddox?
You tell me that.
and I'll leave.
- All's I know is Maddox
was trying to help Kurtis
find a special G-44?
- What's a G-44?
- [laughs]
- You're looking at one.
Ship full of us
and still not the one he wants.
- Sharon.
[door closes]
- Oh. and you must be
the new G-44 clone.
I'm Roger.
- Nice to meet you.
- Do you want to go
for a drink sometime?
- Excuse me?
- It's just that I find that
I'm most compatible with G-44s.
and I don't mean to brag.
but I usually sweep them
off their feet.
I'll grab her legs.
Let's get her to Dr. Morgan
before this wears off.
- Well. I guess everyone's
done playing nice.
- Okay. listen up. team.
The moment we're out of FTL.
the bridge will fire
an EM pulse at "Ark 22."
Once we have confirmation
of a hit.
we'll launch and board.
We should expect
heavy resistance.
- Bridge to Kimi--
we're two minutes out.
Are you ready?
- We're locked and loaded.
bridge.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Wow.
You shouldn't be conscious.
Our metabolism is fantastic.
isn't it?
Triple the dosage
on the sedative.
- [breathing heavily]
- Don't worry.
This won't hurt too much.
[tool whirring]
- [grunts. breathing heavily]
- Where's Garnet?
[breathing heavily]
- Medbay.
- Oh. yeah?
[breathing heavily]
- You don't have to do this.
- Yes. I do. You're the one.
- What does that mean?
[tool whirring]
- Shh.
Go to sleep now.
- Sharon!
[scalpel clatters]
- Ian!
Let's get the hell
off this ship.
- Sasha. you have a handle
on the EM pulse. right?
- Yep.
- Good.
Timing is everything on this.
Leaving FTL
in three. two. one...
Fire EMP. Sasha.
- At what?
There's no sign of "Ark 22."
- Oh. no.
- We can't get a visual
on "Ark 22."
- We're too late.
"Ark 22" has left.
- I asked you to do one thing.
- I know. I'm sorry.
I just saw red.
- That--that
can't happen again.
- It won't.
I-I promise.
- I need to handle this my way.
- I know.
Last thing I would want
to do is hurt you.
Okay?
- Okay.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Why are you looking
at Milan's file?
- I just wanted to see
who we're dealing with.
- We are not dealing with this.
I am.
Why can't you understand that?
- I do.
I do. I'm s--
[sighs]
Sanji.
- I need some time alone.
- Oh. come on.
- I said I need some time.
Or do I need to tell you
that twice. too?
- [scoffs]
- I tried to keep Felix
from searching too far
from the settlement.
but he is determined
to find Angus and Kelly.
- You need to take this
more seriously.
- [sighs]
- I am taking this seriously.
but there's nothing we can do.
- You could have stopped Felix
from searching further.
- Well. it's not like
he's gonna find the two kids.
Ves. we both know
what happened to them.
- Do we?
Because if you're right.
we have a much bigger problem
than we thought.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm